<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>DevOps</title><link href="http://bblakemore312.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://bblakemore312.github.io/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://bblakemore312.github.io/</id><updated>2020-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</updated><entry><title>Dev-Ops</title><link href="http://bblakemore312.github.io/Dev-Ops.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Brandon, Jessica, Ryan</name></author><id>tag:bblakemore312.github.io,2020-01-21:/Dev-Ops.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;DevOps is a new movement/idea of creating a more efficient way of conducting business in IT. It is the idea that in order to make sure development and operations area efficient, you must put the two teams together so that they can hold each other accountable. Work is completed …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;DevOps is a new movement/idea of creating a more efficient way of conducting business in IT. It is the idea that in order to make sure development and operations area efficient, you must put the two teams together so that they can hold each other accountable. Work is completed much more efficiently and faster by having the development and operations teams working together to solve problems. DevOps helps build a better work environment by emphasizing teamwork. Development and operations collaborate more closely under the structure of DevOps due to shared responsibilities and combined workflows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Companies who have restructured their IT departments to adopt this idea of colaboration between development and operations have experienced many benefits as a result. The biggest benefit would be the ability to complete work much faster while also being more accurate. Troubleshooting issues that arise while working on a project/application is faster and more accurate when you have everyone who has worked on creating it/deploying it working together. Having an IT team that is able to keep up with the always changing technological updates is key to having a successful business. &lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Both"></category></entry><entry><title>Development</title><link href="http://bblakemore312.github.io/development.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Brandon, Jessica, Ryan</name></author><id>tag:bblakemore312.github.io,2020-01-21:/development.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;In DevOps, the Development side of the chain normally consists of Creation, Planning, Verifying and Packaging. Development is the first side of the coin in creation of the IT product or application. Almost all Companies in this day and age use and critically need IT departments, along with the devlopment …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In DevOps, the Development side of the chain normally consists of Creation, Planning, Verifying and Packaging. Development is the first side of the coin in creation of the IT product or application. Almost all Companies in this day and age use and critically need IT departments, along with the devlopment of new programs and creation of digital infrastrucutre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The development side of things has more to do with the actual code needed for a project rather than making the product operational. These are the people who write the code and set up the structure/foundation for the product or application they are producing. If the development team does not complete their work effciently, then the operations team cannot get the product/application up and running this role in a company normally consists of software engineers which requires a degree in Computer Science or Software Engineering. &lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="devops"></category></entry><entry><title>Operations</title><link href="http://bblakemore312.github.io/operations.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Brandon, Jessica, Ryan</name></author><id>tag:bblakemore312.github.io,2020-01-21:/operations.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The other side of DevOps, is the Operational side of the chain that is in charge of the network infrastructure, server and device managment, and computer and help desk operations. After the development team is done writing the code and creating an application or product, the operations team works on …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The other side of DevOps, is the Operational side of the chain that is in charge of the network infrastructure, server and device managment, and computer and help desk operations. After the development team is done writing the code and creating an application or product, the operations team works on getting that applicaiton up and running, and able to be used by the customer. The operations team does all the necessary work to finalize the applicaiton/product so that it can reach its end user. This role in a company normally requires a degree in operations management, supply chain management, or another related feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The vale that operations gives to a company is almost immeasurable. Without the final work operations does to fix an y necessary bugs or issues, secure the operational stability and efficiency of the product, customers would have unreliable products that may or may not meet their needs. There are also many current issues or future complications that are avoided becasue they are caught by a second set of eyes when the operations team works to deploy the application or product. Companies rely heavily on operations, just as they do development, because both are necessary to have a profound and productive IT department. &lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="ops"></category></entry></feed>