<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>DevOps - Both</title><link href="http://bblakemore312.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://bblakemore312.github.io/feeds/both.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://bblakemore312.github.io/</id><updated>2020-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</updated><entry><title>Dev-Ops</title><link href="http://bblakemore312.github.io/Dev-Ops.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Brandon, Jessica, Ryan</name></author><id>tag:bblakemore312.github.io,2020-01-21:/Dev-Ops.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;DevOps is a new movement/idea of creating a more efficient way of conducting business in IT. It is the idea that in order to make sure development and operations area efficient, you must put the two teams together so that they can hold each other accountable. Work is completed …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;DevOps is a new movement/idea of creating a more efficient way of conducting business in IT. It is the idea that in order to make sure development and operations area efficient, you must put the two teams together so that they can hold each other accountable. Work is completed much more efficiently and faster by having the development and operations teams working together to solve problems. DevOps helps build a better work environment by emphasizing teamwork. Development and operations collaborate more closely under the structure of DevOps due to shared responsibilities and combined workflows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Companies who have restructured their IT departments to adopt this idea of colaboration between development and operations have experienced many benefits as a result. The biggest benefit would be the ability to complete work much faster while also being more accurate. Troubleshooting issues that arise while working on a project/application is faster and more accurate when you have everyone who has worked on creating it/deploying it working together. Having an IT team that is able to keep up with the always changing technological updates is key to having a successful business. &lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Both"></category></entry></feed>