<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>DevOps - devops</title><link href="http://bblakemore312.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://bblakemore312.github.io/feeds/devops.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://bblakemore312.github.io/</id><updated>2020-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</updated><entry><title>Development</title><link href="http://bblakemore312.github.io/development.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-01-21T00:00:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Brandon, Jessica, Ryan</name></author><id>tag:bblakemore312.github.io,2020-01-21:/development.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;In DevOps, the Development side of the chain normally consists of Creation, Planning, Verifying and Packaging. Development is the first side of the coin in creation of the IT product or application. Almost all Companies in this day and age use and critically need IT departments, along with the devlopment …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In DevOps, the Development side of the chain normally consists of Creation, Planning, Verifying and Packaging. Development is the first side of the coin in creation of the IT product or application. Almost all Companies in this day and age use and critically need IT departments, along with the devlopment of new programs and creation of digital infrastrucutre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The development side of things has more to do with the actual code needed for a project rather than making the product operational. These are the people who write the code and set up the structure/foundation for the product or application they are producing. If the development team does not complete their work effciently, then the operations team cannot get the product/application up and running this role in a company normally consists of software engineers which requires a degree in Computer Science or Software Engineering. &lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="devops"></category></entry></feed>